Guide to the Bruce Maguire / Student YMCA Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Special Subjects, Series VI
  - National Student Caucus: Reports/Policy Records, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 374)
  - National Student Caucus: Printed Material, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 375)
  - National Student Christian Federation (NSCF) )in process of becoming University Student Christian Movement (USCM): Communications, 1965-1967 (Box 33, Folder 376-378)
  - NSCF: Reports/Policy Records, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 379)
  - NSCF: Reports/Policy Records, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 379)
  - NSCF: Printed Material, 1966-1967, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 381)
  - Related Organizations: National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 382)
  - Related Organizations: World Student Christian Federation, 1937-1974 (Box 34, Folder 383)
  - Related Organizations: Miscellaneous A - I (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - Related Organizations: Miscellaneous N - U (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Communications, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 386)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Notes, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 387)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Books, 1929-1971 (Box 34, Folder 388-390)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 391)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Clippings and Articles, 1923-1972, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 392-395)
  - Student Strike Against Racism and Vietnam, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 396)
  - Student YMCA Movement, 1952-1967, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 397)
  - Urban Universities: Commuter Students, 1963-1966, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 398)
  - World War II, War with Japanese:Articles from Los Angeles Examiner, 1943 Nov 11 (Box 35, Folder 399)
  - Poster re. Japanese Evacuation in Calif., 1942 (Box OVd)
  - YMCA on the American Campus: Communications, 1959-1961 (Box 35, Folder 400)
  - YMCA on the American Campus: Reports/Policy Records, 1956-1961, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 401)
  - YMCA on the American Campus: Notes, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 402)
  - YMCA on the American Campus: Printed Material, 1956-1961, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 403)
  - YMCA - Purpose and Development: Communications, 1959-1963, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 404)
  - YMCA - Purpose and Development: Reports/Policy Records, 1956-1964, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 405-406)
  - YMCA - Purpose and Development: Notes, 1963, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 407)
  - YMCA - Purpose and Development: Printed Material, 1949-1963, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 408)
  - YMCA/YWCA Relations: Communications, 1955-1965, n.d (Box 36, Folder 409)
  - YMCA/YWCA Relations: Reports/Policy Records, 1933-1969, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 410-412)
  - YMCA/YWCA Relations: Notes, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 413)
  - YMCA/YWCA Relations: Books, 1959-1970 (Box 36, Folder 414)
  - YMCA/YWCA Relations: Pamphlets, 1962-1973 (Box 36, Folder 415)
  - YMCA/YWCA Relations: Clippings and Articles, 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 416)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA): Communications, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 417)
  - (YWCA): Reports/Policy Records, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 417)
  - (YWCA): Printed Material, 1959, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 417)
  - National Board of YWCAs: Printed Material, 1960-1966, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 418)
- Collected Printed Material, Series VII
  - YMCA Publications
    - International Committee of YMCAs, 1944, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 419)
    - World Council/World Alliance of YMCAs, 1958, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 420)
    - Serials: World Communique, 1961-1964 (Box 37, Folder 421)
    - Serials: Miscellaneous, 1936-1967 (Box 37, Folder 422)
    - Pamphlets, 1958-1970, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 423)
    - Clippings and Articles, 1955-1983, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 424-425)
  - Publications of Related Organizations
    - Department of the Interior War Relocation Authority, 1943-1945 (Box 37, Folder 426)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 427)
    - Presbyterian University Pastors, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 428)
    - Student Christian Movement (British), 1945-1950, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 429)
    - Student Volunteer Movement, 1955, 1959, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 430)
    - United Student Christian Council (incl. Kandy Series) (Box 38, Folder 431)
    - Miscellaneous organizations: A - U (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - Miscellaneous Publications
    - Authors: B - C (Box 38, Folder 433)
    - Authors: H - K (Box 38, Folder 434)
    - Authors: Mil - Min (Box 38, Folder 435)
    - Authors: R - W (Box 38, Folder 436)
- Personal File of Bruce Maguire, Series VIII
  - Correspondence: General, 1954-1985, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 437-438)
  - Correspondence: Job Offers, 1942-1955 (Box 39, Folder 439-440)
  - Pacific Southwest Area Council: Integration between Student Council and Area Board, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - Pacific Southwest Area Council: General, 1953-1954 (Box 39, Folder 442-444)
  - Pacific Southwest Area Council: University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA), 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Notes, 1953, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 446)
  - Notebook #1 (Box 39, Folder 447-450)
  - Notebook #2 (Box 40, Folder 451-453)
  - Biographical information, News Clippings, Personal Items and Memorabilia: Name tag from National Student Assembly (Box 40, Folder 454)
  - Program sponsored by BBM's local church (Box 40, Folder 455)